{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "The 'function' and ' var' are known as:",
      "answers": ["Keywords", "Datatypes", "Declaration Statement", "Prototype"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
      "answers": ["Global Variable", "Local Variable", "Two of the above", "None of the above"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
      "answers": [
        "Mutuable",
        "Dynamic",
        "Voaltile",
        "Immutable"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints",
      "answers": ["exception error", "overflow error", "Display Infinity", "None of the above"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Whats got logged ? const arr = [x => x * 1, x => x * 2, x => x * 3, x => x * 4]console.log(arr.reduce((agg, el) => agg + el(agg), 1)); ",
      "answers": [
        "150",
        "120",
        "80",
        "100"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "random6",
      "answers": ["ans1","ans2","ans3","ans4"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "random7",
      "answers": [
        "ans1",
        "ans2",
        "ans3",
        "ans4"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "random8",
      "answers": [
        "ans1",
        "ans2",
        "ans3",
        "ans4"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "random9",
      "answers": ["ans1","ans2","ans3","ans4"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following is not a reserved word in JavaScript?",
      "answers": [
        "Interface",
        "Throws",
        "Program",
        "Short"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "random11",
      "answers": ["ans1","ans2","ans3","ans4"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "In JavaScript, we do not have datatypes like integer and float. What is the function that can be used to check if the number is an integer or not?",
      "answers": ["ifInteger(value)", "Integer(value)"," isInteger(value)", "None of the above"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}
